intagme.com 2016-06-07

# Instagram Widget | Intagme.com

##  **Instagram Widget** allows you to show your Instagram Photos on your Website. **It's easy and Free!**

Intagme Privacy Policy 

This Privacy Policy describes how Intagme (“We”, “Us”, “Our”) handles your personal information for our services on Intagme website at www.intagme.com (“Site”). By using or accessing the Site, you expressly consent to Our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. 

Information collection and use 

We collect the following personally identifiable information: 

• Your Internet protocol (IP) address;   
• Your browser's User Agent: A User Agent is a short string that web browsers and other applications send to identify themselves to web servers;   
• Information you share with us; 

From time to time, we may ask for and gather additional information from you.If you are a registered user on the Site, We provide you with tools and account settings to remove, access and modify some of the personally identifiable information you provided to us and associated with your account. For example, you may remove access and modify your email address and country of origin. 

We use your personal information only for providing you with better services on the Site. We do not sell your personal information to third parties. However, We do use your email address to send you promotional material. 

Our policy towards children 

Our Site is not directed to children under 13. If you become aware that your child has provided Us with personal information without your consent, please contact Us. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If We become aware that a child under 13 has provided Us with personal information, We take steps to remove such information. 

Log Files and Cookies 

Intagme makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

Intagme does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. 

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on Intagme. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to Intagme and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners uincludes Google Adsense and others. 

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on Intagme send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. Intagme has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Intagme's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites. 

Information Sharing and Disclosure 

We may be required by law enforcement, government administrators, and/or judicial authorities to provide personally identifiable information. We will disclose personally identifiable information upon receipt of a court order, or if required to co-operate with law enforcement, administrative or other governmental agencies. We reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that We in good faith believe to be unlawful. We may also share your personal information with: 

• Our service providers who help with Our business operations and employees on a need-to-know basis.   
• Third parties to whom you explicitly ask Us to send your information or you consent to and are notified when using a specific service.   
• Business entities, if We plan to merge with or be acquired by that business entity, should such a change in control occur.   
Certain information provided by you is displayed throughout the Site (and so available to the public), and is connected to all of your activity on the Site. 

Information Security 

We use commercially reasonable methods to keep personally identifiable information securely in Our files and systems. We do not handle your Instagram passwords directly. We use Instagram's API and OAuth 2.0 protocol to authorize Our users. 

Our databases are secured with passwords to guard against unauthorized access of Our systems. Only engineer staff members may access data on a need-to-know basis. We also use third party security services against malicious attacks such as SQL injection and denial of service (DOS) attacks. 

Third Party Links and Advertising 

We do not sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent. The Site links to other websites that may collect personally identifiable information about you. We also use third party advertising to serve ads when you visit the Site. This privacy policy does not govern collection and use of personal information by third parties. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any other websites to which the Site links or which link to the Site. 

Questions, Suggestions and Modifications to This Privacy Policy 

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or its implementation you may contact Us. This Privacy Policy is subject to change at any time without notice. To make sure you are aware of any changes, please review it periodically.
